<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on OIRA_Web_Reports</title>
    <link>https://betsycc.github.io/OIRA_Web_Reports/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on OIRA_Web_Reports</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://betsycc.github.io/OIRA_Web_Reports/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Customization of Hugo Lithium theme and the datatable function</title>
      <link>https://betsycc.github.io/OIRA_Web_Reports/2020/01/21/customization-of-hugo-lithium-and-datatable-function/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betsycc.github.io/OIRA_Web_Reports/2020/01/21/customization-of-hugo-lithium-and-datatable-function/</guid>
      <description>In the first blog post, How this site was created…, I very briefly described the tools I used to create this draft website. Since then a lot of additional customizations have been made to get the draft to a more finished working state. I wanted to document the basic steps taken and files that needed to be changed in order to customize the tools used to create this site before I forget so that others who are interested in doing something similar or who want to use this draft and make further customizations to suit their own needs will have a starting point to work from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How this site was created...</title>
      <link>https://betsycc.github.io/OIRA_Web_Reports/2019/12/26/how-this-site-was-created/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betsycc.github.io/OIRA_Web_Reports/2019/12/26/how-this-site-was-created/</guid>
      <description>This is my first blog post which I created mostly to test out how the blog would work if we decided to have one.
This website is a draft for testing out options for posting accessible data tables and reports for CUNY’s Office of Institutional Research.
This site was created using RStudio and blogdown using the default blogdown/Hugo theme, hugo-lithium, as a base and then customizing it to be more in line with CUNY’s branding by altering the layouts and CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>